gsmmarhaba.com 2017-04-12

# Privacy Policy | Gsm Marhaba

**Privacy Policy:**  
**Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices**  
**you can make about the way your information is collected and used.**  
**To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.**  
**Log files are maintained and analysed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information**  
**but do capture the user's IP address, which is automatically recognised by our web servers.**  
**  
****Commitment To Children's Privacy:**  
**Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from**  
**those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.**  
**  
****Cookies:**  
**This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission.**  
**Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences.**  
**Cookies are not shared with any third parties.**  
**  
****Contacting Us:**  
**If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.**  
**webmaster@gsmmarhaba.com**
